迈阿密
慢点好吗 迈克 你搞得我不舒服
Hey slow down Mike okay You're making me sick.
如果不是你害我们迟到 我会慢点的
I would slow down if you hadn't already made us late.
我们没迟到好吗 是你太紧张
We're We're not late okay You're just anxious.
不 我紧张是因为你害我们迟到
No I'm anxious 'cause you made us late.
我下半生一定不会和你一起这样做
I'm not doin' this with you in the next phase of our lives.
你必须尊重我的时间
You're gon' respect my time.
我的肚子
My stomach My stomach.
迈克 马上在那家店前停车
Hey Mike look pull over at that store right there.
我需要姜汁汽水
I need a ginger ale.
我们没时间买姜汁汽水 老兄
Look we don't have no time to get no ginger ale man.
别这样 迈克 我不舒服
Come on Mike I'm sick.
你吓死我了 知道吗
You're freaking me out okay
我觉得我快要吐了
I feel like I'm gonna throw throw up.
我挑战你 马克斯
I dare you Marcus.
你有90秒 知道吗
You got 90 seconds all right
只能买姜汁汽水
Ginger ale and nothing else.
我是个成人好吗
I am a grown ass man okay
对我好点吧
Just be nice.
好吧 85秒
Oh Okay 85 seconds.
那些热狗新鲜吗
Are those dogs fresh
昨天才摆出来的
I put 'em on yesterday.
给我一个 上面放点佐料和芥末
Well give me one and put some relish and some mustard on that motherfucker.
拿起来 来 快点
Hook it up Come on hurry up.
不 那边那个 对 那个 快点
No that one right there Yeah Yeah that right there Hurry up.
该走了
Gotta go gotta go.
别慢吞吞的
Don't be takin' your time.
对 就这样嘛
Yeah my man.
打开收银机
Hey open the register.
禁止逗留
不 马上
No no no Now
先生 你选错日子了
Sir today is not the day.
闭嘴
Shut the fuck up
看 如果我不在15秒之内上车
Look if I'm not in that car in 15 seconds
有个脾气暴躁的男人会进来 我们都完蛋了
there's a very surly man that's comin' in here and we both are fucked.
马克斯 别动
Marcus Hey don't fuckin' move.
过去
The fuck over there
迈克 我跟这人说了我必须走了
'Ey Mike I told this guy I had to go.
柜台上那是彩虹糖吗 马克斯
Is that Skittles on the counter Marcus
他花了很久时间卖我姜汁汽水
Well he was takin' a long time with the ginger ale.
不对 他进来时就马上拿了姜汁汽水
That is incorrect He grabbed that ginger ale the second he came in here.
禁止逗留
不对 他进来时就马上拿了姜汁汽水
That is incorrect He grabbed that ginger ale the second he came in here.
禁止逗留
是热狗吗 马克斯
A hot dog Marcus
你根本不该吃那鬼东西
You're not supposed to be eatin' that shit.
这不是我的 迈克 对 给你的
This is not mine Mike Yes it is.
你别多管闲事
Mind your business with your tattletaling ass.
大家都闭嘴
Everybody shut the fuck up
先生 你必须把武器放下
Sir I'm gonna need you to lower your weapon.
不然你来拿我的武器吧
Come take my weapon then motherfucker.
别跟他作对
Don't antagonise him.
马克斯 上车
Marcus get in the car.
迈克 他拿枪指着我的头
Mike he has a gun to my head.
你想对付他 还是我
Wanna deal with him you wanna deal with me
抱歉 先生 我必须走了
Sorry sir but I gotta go.
你不必向他开枪 迈克
You didn't have to shoot him Mike.
上车
Get in the car.
打911
Call 911.
你们不是警察
Aren't you the police
绝 地 战 警 生死与共
别人眼里的你
Other people look at you
看到的是量身定制的西装 汽车 手表
and see the tailored suits the cars the watches.
我们相识时 那一切都不存在
I met you without any of that.
一丝不挂 基本上是赤身裸体
Stripped basically naked
那是90%我嫁给你的原因
which is 90% of why I'm marrying you.
我在你最低谷时遇见了你
I met you at your lowest.
你中了枪
You'd been shot.
但你内心的火
But there was a fire in you that was
是非凡的
extraordinary.
我发誓要用余生来煽动那股火焰
And I vow to spend the rest of my life fanning that flame.
现在我宣布
I now pronounce you
你们结为夫妻
husband and wife.
你可以吻新娘
You may kiss the bride.
太好了
Yes
我好喜欢
I love it.
他在中枪后与治疗师结婚是有道理的
You know it kinda makes sense that he married his therapist after he got shot.
我喜欢他一点 心理健康非常重要
I love that for him Mental health is super important.
那是他的物理治疗师
Well it was his physical therapist.
恭喜 迈克 丽塔 谢谢你
Congratulations Michael Rita Thank you thank you.
市长先生
Mr Mayor.
说早了就不灵了 我仍然只是个卑微的美国律师
Oh not yet Don't jinx it I'm still just a lowly US Attorney.
我一直在关注你的工作
I've been watching what you're doin'.
我支持你 谢谢
You got my vote Thank you.
恭喜你
Congratulations to you.
你们就是金童玉女
I mean the definition of a power couple right there.
我去帮你拿饮料 好
I'll grab you a drink Okay.
你想要什么吗 不 不需要 谢谢
Can I get you anything No I'm good thank you.
一直以来 我都以为你至死都是单身汉
And all this time I thought you were a terminal bachelor.
这一次我自己也始料不及
I I I even surprised myself with this one.
我想你一直没遇见对的人
Yeah I guess you just hadn't met the right one.
那时候我还有待成长
I had some growing up to do.
当时你已经50岁了
You were 50.
好
Okay.
我得为他所说的一切预先道歉
I'm gonna pre apologise for whatever he says.
迈克
Mike.
不行 你也知道的 马克斯
No you know how it is Don't Marcus
马克斯 让我说出来
Marcus Come Let me get it out
别这样 兄弟
Come on man.
你经历了那么多 好吧
Everything you have been through man Okay.
女巫 巫师
The witch The Bruja.
妓女
The prostitute.
我妹妹 记得吗 你应该跟我说我妹妹的事 迈克
My sister 'Member You coulda told me about my sister Mike.
你早该告诉我的
You coulda told me that.
如果她对你有感觉 我会拥抱你的
I would've embraced you if that's who she was feeling.
我爱你 迈克 无庸置疑
I love you Mike No doubt.
如果警监还活着 他一定想亲眼目睹这一幕
You know Cap would've loved to have been here to see this.
但你知道吗
But you know what
我们找到了他的女儿朱迪和孙女凯莉
We got his daughter Judy and his granddaughter Callie.
她有话想说
She wants to say something.
我爷爷很爱大家
My grandad loved you guys.
如果他在这里 他会说不要把这件事搞砸
And if he were here he would have told you not to F this up.
他会这么说的
That's what he would've said.
是啊 他会说 别搞砸了
Yeah he woulda said Don't fuck it up
没错
Exactly.
抱歉我说脏话了
Oh excuse me.
嘿
'Ey.
迈克 我们成为拍档一段时间了
Mike you been my partner a long time.
是 先生
Yes sir.
现在他将成为你的伴侣 克莉斯丁
Now he's gonna be your partner Christine.
祝贺迈克和克莉斯丁·劳瑞
To Mike and Christine Lowrey.
一辈子 一辈子
For life For life
加油 马克斯
Go Marcus Go Marcus Go Marcus Go Marcus
糟了
Oh shit.
发生什么事了
What happened What happened
马克斯
Marcus Marcus
这里的地址是什么
What's the address
让我进去 退后
Let me in let me in let me in Back up.
我是丽塔·塞卡达警监 有一名警官心脏骤停
This is Captain Rita Secada I have an officer in cardiac arrest.
加油
Come on man.
你的死期还没到
It's not your time.
马克斯
Marcus
马克
Marc Marc
这家伙
This guy.
哥们
Hey buddy.
你在干什么
What you doing
我一生都在害怕之中 迈克
I spent my whole life being scared Mike.
我浪费了太多时间
I wasted so much time.
请你从边缘退后一点
Why Why Why don't you Why don't you just step back from the edge a little bit please.
现在是哪一年
What year is it
是星期二
It's Tuesday.
你扭着屁股昏倒的同一年
Same year your ass was wobbling in.
哇 感觉已经有五年了
Oh wow Felt like it was five years.
我处于海洋的底部
I was in the basement of the ocean.
我所有的烦恼都消失了
All my bullshit was gone.
唯有自由
Just freedom.
还有完全充满爱 迈克
And full body love Mike Full body love.
好
Okay.
不如你
Why Why Why don't you
以爱让你全身从边缘回来好吗
love your full body back from the ledge please
没什么好怕的
Nothing to be scared of.
我的时间还没到 宝贝
It's not my time baby It's not my time.
伯内特先生
Mr Burnett
我看着他
Hey I got him.
他只是
He's just
我不知道他到底在干嘛
I don't know what the fuck he's doing.
但我看着他了 我们没事
But I got it I got him We're good We are good.
我们很好
We are great 'Ey
迈阿密
Miami
305一辈子
305 for life
唰唰
Kakow
停 你那东西会闪瞎别人的眼睛
All right Just stop You gon' put somebody's eye out with that thing man.
我在唤醒我的原始能量 迈克
I'm bringing the thunder Mike I get it.
唤醒能量
Bringing the thunder.
好 就是这样
All right There you go.
来抱抱
Oh man Bring it in.
我以为我已经失去你了 兄弟
Thought I lost you brother.
你的人生少不了我
Couldn't lose me if you tried.
你知道你的屁股露出了吧
You know your ass is out right
大家的屁股都露出来了 迈克
Everybody's ass is out Mike.
嘿
Hey.
一场暴风雨要来了
There's a storm coming.
不 不是那种暴风雨
No Not that kind of storm.
你会经受考验
You're gonna be tested.
事情会变得糟糕
Things are gonna get bad
你将不得不做出一个非常艰难的选择
and you're gonna have to make a really hard choice.
你只需记住 你很厉害
Just know you're good.
这是我的私人时间 麦格拉斯先生
This is my private time Mr McGrath.
请问有什么能帮到你的吗
How may I help you
我要你转一些钱 你的钱
I need you to move some money Your money
其实是你老板的 我要贩毒集团现金
Your boss's actually I need it to be cartel cash.
不到两千万
Just under 20 million.
回溯那账户从2004年到2020年1月的
Backdated series of transfers beginning 2004 ending January 2020
一系列
into
转账
that account.
以已故康拉德·霍华德警监的名义
In the name of the late Captain Conrad Howard.
我有负责物流的人
I have people who can handle logistics.
我只需要你的登录信息
I really just need your log in credentials.
我为什么要给你这些
And why would I give you those
天啊
Oh my God
过来 亲爱的
Come here darling.
来
Come on.
过来
Come here.
【面部识别】
手机无法转账
You can't transfer funds from a phone.
亲爱的 怎么了
Hey honey what's going on
她们互相认识吗
Do they know each other
亲爱的 谁在你身边
Honey who's there with you
好 亲爱的
All right all right Honey
转账开始了
Here we go.
资金转移 转至:康拉德·霍华德
他们会为此杀了你
They'll kill you for this.
他们不会知道事情的经过
They're not even gonna know this happened.
你的女友听见你和你太太的电话
Your girlfriend heard you on the phone with your wife
发现你根本没打算和她离婚
and realised you were never gonna divorce her.
她一怒之下开枪射杀了你
And in a fit of passion she shot you.
你的保镖试图介入 但已经来不及了
Your bodyguard tried to step in but he was too late.
当她意识到她那恐怖的行为
And realising the horror of her actions
她自杀了
she took her own life.
不要
No
亲爱的 你在干什么
Honey what are you doing
两星期前你才心脏病发作 没错
You had a heart attack two weeks ago Exactly.
他们称其为寡妇制造者是有原因的 你该留在医院 宝贝
They call it a widow maker for a reason You need to be in the hospital baby.
我尝试说过他了
Hey I tried to told his ass T.
显然 他已经是成年人了 他获准自行出院
Apparently he's an adult He was allowed to sign hisself out.
宝贝 别这样 我一刻也无法忍受离开你
Hey babe Look come on I couldn't take one more second away from you.
我体内的支架让我血脉喷张
All these stents in me got my blood flowing.
我在回家途中 好吧
I'm on D way All right now.
拜托 那是我的电话
Ey Ey Come on man That's my phone.
我爱你 马克斯 我们10分钟后到
I love you Marcus We'll be there in 10.
好的 宝贝 爱你
All right babe All right Love you.
嘿 迈克
Hey Mike.
我没打算告诉你
I wasn't even gonna tell you this
但我们不是第一次了
but this ain't the first time we done this.
我们时常同车 你是什么意思
We ride together all the time what you mean
不 我是说我们的灵魂
No I'm talking about our souls.
我们曾一起同车 但我看到了全部 迈克
You know we've ridden together but I saw it all Mike.
我们注定携手同行 已经做了好几辈子的生死搭档
We're bound And we have been for lifetimes.
我们并不总是叫迈克和马克斯 但我们的灵魂不曾改变
We haven't always been Mike and Marcus but we've always been us.
你在说什么
What you talking 'bout
我们是灵魂伴侣
We're soulmates.
是 是的
Yup Yeah.
不
Naw.
我认为的灵魂伴侣看起来有点不同
Yeah I kind of I saw my soulmate looking a little different than that.
迈克 你被困在肉体里
See See Mike you stuck in the physical.
灵魂没有鸡鸡
Souls don't have dicks.
我蛮肯定我的灵魂有鸡鸡 马克斯
I'm pretty sure my soul has a dick Marcus.
看吧 就是这些废话 所以我们才被困住
See That's that shit right there That's why we're stuck.
我本来也没打算告诉你这个
You know I wasn't gonna tell you this shit either
但我的灵魂比你的先进多了
but my soul is more advanced than your soul.
我不是说你的灵魂很笨
It's not that your soul is stupid.
知道吗
You know
只是你比较像是婴儿灵魂 知道吗
It's just that you're more like a baby soul You know
而我比较像是母亲的灵魂
And I'm more like a mother soul.
我只想给你喂奶
And I just gotta suckle ya.
知道吗 让你吸奶
You know Put you on that titty.
知道吗
You know
你觉得你的大脑缺氧多久了
Hey How long you think your brain went without oxygen
爸爸 爸爸回来了
Daddy Daddy's home.
宝贝 宝贝 你回来了 我的家人呢 我的家庭
Baby Oh baby you're back Where my family My family.
嗨 宝贝
Hey baby.
小马克斯
Little Marcus
跟奶奶和爷爷说嗨
Say hi to Pop pop Say hi to Grandad.
我好想你 你看你 女人
I missed you so Look at you woman.
不 别这样 看着我 宝贝
No come on look at me baby.
我们得让他们冷静下来
We're gonna have to hose them down.
好 我们知道了
All right All right we get it We get it.
放点冰在你的内裤什么的
Put some ice in your drawers or somethin'.
真好笑
That's funny.
你感觉好吗 马克斯
Are you feeling good Marcus
我一生中从未感觉如此好过
I never felt better in my life.
马克斯 我太想你了 亲爱的 但你必须休息
Oh Marcus I missed you so much honey but you need to get some rest.
不 宝贝 我需要你
Oh no baby I need you.
让我去补充一些电解质 好的 宝贝 给我一个吻
Just let me get some electrolytes Okay baby Give me a kiss.
我爸爸怎么了
So what's going on with my dad
他赤裸地站在屋顶上
Well he was on the roof naked
他还说他去了海床
and he said he had been at the basement of the ocean.
神奇鹰嘴豆
Amazing Chickpeas
还有 他说我有个很笨的婴孩灵魂
Oh and he said I have a stupid baby soul
也没有鸡鸡
with no penis.
你们必须和他谈谈
嘿 雷吉 是 长官
Hey Reggie Yes sir.
你吃了我的零食 没有 长官
Did you eat my snacks No sir.
我正期待着我的零食 雷吉
I was looking forward to my snacks Reggie.
亲爱的
Honey.
你知道吗 你该去找份工作
You know what You need to get a job.
我是一名美国海军陆战队员 长官
I'm a US Marine sir.
那么你该被调派出去
Well then you need to deploy.
我们刚从也门回来
You know we just got back from Yemen.
谢谢你为国效力
Thank you for your service.
你以为我死了 对吗 死了
You thought I was dead didn't you Dead
有一件事你不知道 雷吉
One thing you don't know Reggie.
我在这安了一台监控 对吧
I got a camera up in here Yeah.
特丽莎
Theresa
是医生吩咐的 马克斯 你要严格节食 无盐 无糖 无脂肪
It's the doctor's orders Marcus You're on a strict diet No salt no sugar no fats.
不能有压力 吵闹声 消耗体力
No stress no loud noises no physical exertion.
你随便坐下就是了
Just sit your ass down somewhere man.
告诉他 迈克
Tell him Mike.
还有 亲爱的 我和你一起做 现在我们是素食者
And honey I'm doing it with you We're now vegetarians.
素食者 看着我
Vegetarians Look at me.
你看我这体魄 宝贝 我现在宛如新生
Look at all this man baby I'm brand new.
我需要动物糖分来生存
I need animal sugars to survive.
宝贝
Well baby
我留了沙拉给你
I have a salad for you.
沙拉
A salad
特丽莎 看来一切在你掌控之中 我的任务也完成了
Hey T looks like you got this under control My tour of duty is done.
再见 克莉斯丁 再见 迈克 再见 两位
Bye Christine Bye Mike Bye guys.
迈克 等一下
Hey Mike Wait up Wait up wait up.
你要去做什么 能帮我跑一下腿吗
What you about to do Can you run a quick quick for me
好 你需要什么
Yeah what you need
我会给你$1000 买一些彩虹糖
I'll give you $1 000 for some Skittles.
马克斯 我不会买糖给你
Marcus I am not buying your ass no candy man.
好 $2000 迈克 再来点叮当蛋糕 这可是极高的报价
Okay $2 000 Mike for some Ding Dongs And that's my final offer.
你别想有叮当了
I think you're gonna be Ding Dong less
就如我的灵魂一样
like my soul.
你总是带走我爱的人
You always take whoever I love.
我是迈克·劳瑞警探
This is Detective Mike Lowrey.
警监倒下了
The Captain is down.
他是我儿子
He's my son.
你的家庭一团糟 迈克
You got a fucked up family Mike.
【突发新闻】
司法部一直对迈阿密警察局的贪污问题进行调查
The Department of Justice has been investigating the corruption in the Miami Police Department.
现在我们拥有可靠的情报
And we now have credible intelligence
当年是康拉德·霍华德警监指挥警员
that Captain Conrad Howard was directing these elements
与贩毒集团合作
in coordination with the cartels.
不 我对大约什么时候不感兴趣
No I'm not interested in approximately what time.
我需要知道确切时间 明白吗
I need to know exactly what time do you understand
你一直知道这件事
You knew about this
我两个星期前才知道
I found out two weeks ago.
记者会说的 是真的吗
A press conference Really
我很遗憾你们通过这种方式得知
I'm sorry about the way you had to find out.
但考虑到你们的密切关系 我们的密切关系
But given your closeness Our closeness
如果没有霍华德警监 你们谁也没有工作
Neither one of y'all would have a job if it wasn't for Captain Howard.
丽塔 你知道事情不是这样的
Rita you know this is not true.
坦白说 我不知道
Honestly I don't.
调查发现了新的证据
The investigation has turned up new evidence.
迈阿密执法部门多年来出了不少岔子
Miami law enforcement's been a leaky ship for years now.
证人死亡 线人失踪
Witnesses turn up dead informants disappear.
事件看起来是随机的 直到你汇总几年内发生的事
Events appear random until you aggregate them over a period of years.
然后就会看见一种模式
Then a pattern emerges.
他是谁
Who is this
巴德·格莱斯 联邦调查局局长 此次调查组的领导
Bud Grice FBI heading up the JTF on this show.
这就是我
That's who I am.
我们知道有人在提供情报
Now we knew someone was providing intelligence
给运毒品到南佛罗里达州的毒贩
to a cartel moving product into South Florida.
我们只是不知道是谁
We just didn't know who.
两周前 一名毒品集团的银行家被女友枪杀身亡
A cartel banker turned up dead two weeks ago shot by his girlfriend.
他们找到一部手机 上面有霍华德的联系方式
They found a phone with Howard's contact on it.
与毒贩多年的联系 还有海外银行账户信息
Years of communication with the cartel account references offshore.
在霍华德的名下有数百万美元
Millions in Howard's name.
通过这些证据 终于可以给那贪腐的混蛋定罪了
Final piece we needed to nail that dirty motherfucker.
格莱斯 噢 哇 听我说
Grice Oh whoa Hey hey let me holler at you.
你知道他倒下时我就在他身边 对吗
You know I was with him when he went down right
你再说他贪腐试试
Call him dirty one more time.
你有种就说
I dare you.
我们知道还有其他人和他一伙 我们也会找到他们
We know he had others who were with him We're gonna find them too.
和他一伙的人是我
I was with him.
现在就给我上手铐 我当时和他在一起 迈克
Put the cuffs on me right now I was with him Mike.
不 这些混蛋认为他死了 无法替自己辩护
No these motherfuckers think that just 'cause he's dead and can't defend hisself
就把所有问题推到他身上 毁了他的传奇
they gon' dump all this shit on him burn his legacy.
有我在就不行
Not on my watch.
我是朱迪·霍华德 美国法警
This is Judy Howard US Marshals.
我知道我在这里没有管辖权
I realise I have no jurisdiction here.
但出于职业礼貌
But as a professional courtesy
我想申请了解针对我父亲的指控的来源
I'd like to request visibility into the sources of the allegations against my father.
朱迪
Judy.
我们会解决这问题的 好吗
We're gonna figure this shit out all right
凯莉还好吗
How's Callie
你觉得呢 迈克
How do you think Mike
我们都在同一条船 朱迪
We're on the same team here Judy.
当然不是 迈克
Like hell we are Mike.
如果不是你的混蛋儿子 我爸爸应该还活着
My dad would still be alive if it weren't for your bastard son.
朱迪
Judy
如果我在街上见到他 我以我父亲发誓
If I ever catch him out on the street I swear on my father
我会杀了他
I will put him down.
我们走吧
Come on Come on man Come on.
【迈阿密警察局】
接下来该怎么办
So what's our next move
【迈阿密警察局】
他们说他和毒贩合作 我们去问毒贩吧
They said he was working with the cartel Let's ask the cartel.
联邦监狱 佛罗里达州中部
你好吗
How you doin'
这里是监狱
It's prison.
是的
Yeah.
听好 我们需要你的帮忙
Look We need your help.
他们说霍华德警监贪污
They're saying that Captain Howard was dirty.
你是否有情报
Do you know anything about that
这个情报能让我减刑多少 我还在争取
How much time I get off for this one I'm still working on that.
我在告诉你 我需要你的帮忙
This is me telling you that I need you.
我需要知道 霍华德警监是否与贩毒集团合作
I need to know if Captain Howard was working with the cartels.
没有
No.
他正在调查那些有合作的人
He was onto the ones that were.
所以他被追杀
So he got greenlit.
等等 不
Wait no.
不 霍华德警监被杀 是因为他在你母亲的暗杀名单上
No Captain Howard was killed because he was on your mother's hit list.
他是被加上去的
He was added to it.
你们的人希望看起来像我们做的一样
Your people wanted it to look like us.
你们希望他死去
Your people wanted him dead.
你说 我们的人 是什么意思
Whatchu mean our people
你应该小心
You should be careful.
你在玩游戏 但你连规则都不知道
You're playing a game and you don't even know the rules.
你那边有卑鄙的玩家 你乱说
There's dirty players on your side That's bullshit.
等等 是谁
Wait who
我见过他一次
I saw him one time.
你能认出他吗 当然
Can you ID him Sí.
给我名字
Give me a name.
我不知道他的名字
I don't know his name.
我母亲
My mother.
她就是与他对接的人
She's the one who dealt with him.
我就知道我们该让那巫女活着
I knew we should have kept that damn witch alive.
马克斯
Marcus.
愿她安息
May she rest in peace.
老兄
Dude.
嘿 老板
Hey boss.
登陆 迈阿密市警察局
嘿 老板
Hey boss.
登陆 迈阿密市警察局
线人在联合特遣部队档案中 拿到了霍华德的所有记录
Our man on the inside got all of Howard's records in the JTF file.
登陆 迈阿密市警察局
线人在联合特遣部队档案中 拿到了霍华德的所有记录
Our man on the inside got all of Howard's records in the JTF file.
电脑 手机 文件 所有一切
Computers phones files all of it.
我们知道霍华德曾调查我们的行动
Well we know Howard was onto our operation.
只是不知道他查到多少 别错过任何线索
We just don't know how much he had We need to make sure we got every trace.
很好
That's beautiful.
嘿 老板
Hey boss.
都是纸质文件 到目前为止都没问题
It's all the paper files They're clean so far.
两个手机没问题 他办公室电脑是空的
Two phones had nothing His office computer was empty.
他很小心 但是
He was careful But
但他的旧个人笔记本电脑加密程度较弱
But his old personal laptop had weak encryption.
有了
Here we go.
【网络故障】
糟糕 我们遇倒了 防入侵装置
Shit We tripped a fail safe.
【网络故障】
糟糕 我们遇倒了 防入侵装置
Shit We tripped a fail safe.
什么意思 我们
The fuck you mean we
向外发送了数据
Something was sent.
给谁
To who
短信 [已发送]
我正在追踪接收电话
Tracing the phone now.
短信 [已发送]
【霍华德警监】
搞什么
What the hell
他正在从另一世界给我们发短信
He's texting us from the other side.
不 他没有 马克斯
No he's not Marcus.
如果你看到这个
If you're seeing this
我大概已经死了
I'm probably dead.
该死
Fuck
我真倒霉
Fuck me.
在我开始之前
Before I begin
我想说一件事:
I wanna say one thing:
我正让你们陷入致命的危险
I'm putting you in mortal danger.
各位
Boys
我们组织内有内奸
we got rats in our walls.
但我必须确保你们是我的坏孩子
But I gotta make sure you're my bad boys.
可乐瓶巨人就是关键
The Coke bottle giant is the key.
什么
What
别相信任何人
Don't trust anybody.
那是什么 什么意思 可乐瓶巨人
What's that What does that mean The Coke bottle giant
弗莱彻
Fletcher.
完了
Oh shit.
就是他们
These are the guys.
应该给这些混蛋一枪 彻底解决
We should put a bullet in these motherfuckers Be done with it once and for all.
林茨 我爱你 任由你处置他们当然好
Lintz I love you I'd like nothing more than to let you loose on them.
但死去更多警察对我们没有任何好处
But extra dead cops doesn't do us any favours here.
持续监视 看看他们是否有所行动
Keep them under constant surveillance and see if they make a move.
【艺术走廊】
弗莱彻的仓库就在那条巷子
Fletcher's warehouse is right down that alley.
迈克 我没打算告诉你这件事
Mike I wasn't even gonna tell you this.
那就别告诉我
Then don't tell me.
不 你一定要听 这很重要
No you gotta hear this This is big.
我死不了
I can't die.
什么
What
我死不了
I cannot die.
几周前你在我的婚礼上死得还不错
Motherfucker you did a pretty good job of dying at my wedding a couple weeks ago.
但我没死
But I didn't.
看吧
Watch.
嘿 马克斯
Hey Marcus.
喂 快 滚出马路
Hey Come on Get out of the road
喂
Hey
马克斯
Hey Marcus
停
Hey stop stop.
马克斯
Hey hey Marcus
你这是疯了吗
What are you some kind of moron
停
Stop stop stop.
警察 停车
Police Stop
喂 老兄
Hey Bro
慢点
Slow down
走斑马线
Crosswalk
跟我说话
Talk to me.
你要相信 迈克
You gotta trust Mike.
相信自己 相信宇宙
Trust yourself Trust the universe.
你够了 马克斯
Stop that shit Marcus.
我的时间还没到 迈克
It's not my time Mike.
好 你是说如果我对你的脸开枪
Oh okay So you're saying that if I shoot you in your face
你是说你不会死
you're saying that you won't die.
命运注定你不会朝我脸上开枪
Fate dictates that you won't shoot me in the face.
我是说你说了
I'm saying I'm I'm saying that you saying
如果我对你的脸开枪 你不会死
that if I shoot you in your face are you saying you won't die
命运不做假设 迈克
Fate doesn't deal in hypotheticals Mike.
混蛋 别站在马路中间
我要报警了
I'm gonna call the police.
他们已经到了 女士 别多管闲事
They're already here ma'am Mind your business.
到海滩去吧
Just go to the beach.
别再胡闹了 马克斯
Stop that shit Marcus.
看吧 你把枪收起来了
See You're putting your gun away.
他把枪收起来了
He's putting his gun away.
迈克
Ooh Mike.
专心点
Focus man.
我称这地方为黑人想象的创意空间
Yeah I call this place you know Creative Space for Black Imagination.
弗莱彻
You know that Fletcher.
我的天
Oh my God.
谢谢你
Thank you.
这到底是什么地方
What the hell is this place
这是我的画廊工作室 我现在是一名艺术家
This is my studio gallery I'm an artiste now.
拜托 你才不是艺术家
Please you ain't no damn artist.
你们要什么 霍华德警监
What do you guys want Captain Howard.
是 很遗憾听到他的遭遇 他改善了我的人生
Yeah I was sorry to hear what happened to him He helped turn my life around.
他叫我们找你谈
He told us to talk to you.
好 跟我谈
Okay Talk to me.
我刚刚就和你谈了 那就说你该说的话
I just talked to you Then say what you're supposed to say.
我已经说了我该说的话 你没有
I said what I'm supposed to say You didn't.
那告诉我该说什么 我已经说了我能说的话
Then tell me what I'm supposed to say I've said all I can say.
你在耍我们吗 豆秆
Fucking with us beanstalk
马克斯 别这样
Marcus Come on
霍华德警监救了我的命 我不会搞砸这事的
Captain Howard saved my life I'm not messing this up.
我不能说我该说的 直到你说了你该说的为止
I can't say what I supposed to say until you say what you supposed to say.
直接告诉我们你该说的话
Fletcher just tell us what you supposed to tell us.
笨蛋 听好了
Dumbasses Look.
霍华德警监正在调查一件大事
Captain Howard was onto something big.
他不相信你们这笨蛋会解决 所以他联络了我
He didn't trust that you dumb fucks would figure it out so he contacted me.
因为你们很笨 而我是天才
Because you're stupid and I'm a genius.
所以我用某个东西保护着那资料
So I protected the information in something.
用一个很美的东西
In something beautiful.
再动一下你的脸 再动一下
Flex your face one more time Flex it again
我会打爆你的头
I will blow your fucking head off.
你能停吗 拜托
Would you stop Come on.
在一个会永远活着的东西里面
In something that will live forever.
你开枪了
Did you shoot him
我不认为是我
I don't think so.
别动
Freeze
马克斯
Marcus Marcus
你中枪了
You hit
没有
Nah ah.
黑色软糖 没有人喜欢那玩意儿
Black jellybean Nobody likes that shit.
哇
Whoa.
喂 停止那蠢事
Hey Stop that stupid shit
我没跟你开玩笑 停
I'm not fucking with you Stop
不要
No No no No No
我所向披靡
I don't give a fuck
马克斯 不要
Marcus No No
你在干什么
What are you doing
让我来 但你不行
I got this But you don't though.
不
No No
马克
Marc
走吧 我们走
Let's go Let's move
马克斯
Marcus
伯内特和劳瑞在11街向北移动
Burnett and Lowrey are moving north on 11th.
迈阿密警察 快开
Miami PD Go
你在干什么 我正在打击犯罪 宝贝
What are you doing I'm fightin' crime baby
别动
Freeze
迈克
Mike
你以前有过恐慌发作吗
Have you ever had a panic attack before
什么 没人恐慌发作
What Ain't nobody have no damn panic attack.
你的血压165/90了 出汗 恶心 看心理医生并不丢人
You're at 165 over 90 Sweaty Nauseous There's no shame in getting counselling.
好 谢谢你的关心 兄弟
All right Thank you Appreciate you brother.
迈克 乖乖听医生的话
Mike let the man do his job.
做得好
Good job man.
嘿 迈克
Hey Mike.
你为什么会恐慌
What the hell you panicking about
我不想说
I'm not speaking to you.
我做了什么
What'd I do
你们两个没事吧
You two all right
迈克恐慌发作
Mike had a panic attack.
他没有 迈克没事
He didn't Mike is fine.
发生什么事
What happened
丽塔 你不会相信这件事 但我们收到一个信
Rita you ain't gonna believe this shit But we got a text
一个线报 我们收到线报称弗莱彻违反了假释规定
A tip We got a tip that Fletcher had violated his parole.
所以我们来这里
So we came down here
显然他陷入了一些与他无关的事
and obviously he was into some shit he ain't have no business.
是真的吗 马克斯
Is that true Marcus
你知道我一直和迈克一起
Well you know I was with Mike.
在所有人中 你怎么会认为霍华德警监做不法之事
How could you of all people think Captain Howard was dirty.
我不希望这是真的
I don't want this to be true.
但做好自己的事 尊重证据对大家都有好处
But it would benefit all of us to do our jobs and follow the evidence.
你认为他蠢到把账户记在自己名下
And you think he was stupid enough to put accounts in his own name.
他是被陷害的 被谁
He's being framed By who
这就是我们想要找出的答案
That's what we're trying to find out.
丽塔 拜托 你不会那么傻
Rita come on you're smarter than this.
迈克 请别忘记你正和你的上司说话
Michael please do not forget you're talking to your boss.
我在努力保护你
I'm trying to protect you here.
我们没有两个街区半径的录像
I got no footage for a two block radius.
什么
What
他们肯定毁了所有闭路电视和安保摄像头
They must've killed all CCTV all security cams.
我什么也找不到
I got nothing.
至少他们没拍摄到你的恐慌发作
At least they ain't film your panic attack.
各位
Hey guys.
你恐慌发作了吗 没有
You had a panic attack No.
你要的话 我能推荐一位好的辅导员 不用 东恩 谢谢
If you want I can recommend a good counsellor I'm good Dorn Thanks.
看 这是我拍的 一帧一帧看
Look I shot this went frame by frame.
看这个
Check it out.
好 不在这里
All right Not here.
东恩 关了它 好
Dorn shut it down Yeah.
我们走
Hey Let's go.
这是什么
So what is this
我们不肯定
We're not exactly sure.
哇 哇
Whoa Wow.
这就对了
There you go There you go.
好 现在我知道是你们
All right you fucks Now that I know it's you
是这样的:
here it is:
我不知道最高涉及到哪个高层 但我们这边有贪官
I don't know how high up it goes but there's corrupt officials on our side.
而且他们和贩毒集团合作
And they're working with the cartel.
大约九年前 这一切开始变得很奇怪
This all started smelling funny about nine years ago.
我们准备突袭的那批毒品失踪了
That shipment of coke we were about to raid went missing.
上头一直阻挡我
You know I kept getting shut down from above.
所以我找了已退休的桑切斯和鲁伊斯
So I pulled Sanchez and Ruiz outta retirement.
我让他们从旁调查
I had 'em working on the outside you know
一周后 他们在一场车祸中丧生
They were killed in a car crash a week later.
这让我很震惊
That shook me up.
所以我从未让你们俩插手
And it's why I never brought you two in.
你们原本可以救我 我却担心你们的安全 真丢脸
Well shame on me for worrying about your asses when you coulda saved mine.
但现在由你们决定
But now it's up to you.
还记得2003年的逮捕行动吗
Remember the bust back in 2003
142公斤摇头丸
314 pounds of ecstasy
我收在储存柜 没有记录在案
Well I held onto the storage unit off the books.
那就是真正的文件所在的地方
That's where the real files are.
消灭这些混蛋所需的一切
Everything you need to exterminate these rat fucks.
都在里面
It's in there
你们必须完成我无法做到的事
You're gonna have to finish what I couldn't.
拜托你们
Please.
拜托了 两位
Please boys.
你们是我最后的希望
You're my last hope.
2003年
2003.
那是海地人 佐伊·庞德
That was the Haitians Zoe Pound.
他们的储物柜在哪里
Where was their storage locker
我不知道
I have no idea.
好 你们该去警察局调出我们的案卷原件档案
All right We need you guys to go down to the station and pull our original case files.
我们就能找出储物柜在哪里
That'll tell us where the locker is.
低调并小心地做 我们不知道谁可以信任
Do it quietly and be careful We don't know who we can trust.
这可是大件事
Shit this is heavy man.
我有些很重要的事要说
I just got something important to say.
我就直接说吧 澄清一下
I'm just gonna come out with it Clear the air.
那个内奸不是我
The rat is not me.
谢谢你 东恩
Thanks for that Dorn.
我觉得安全多了
I feel safer.
【监狱 高度设防活动操场】
他们刚打算杀了我儿子
They just tried to kill my son.
因为阿曼多可以证明霍华德警监是无辜的
Because Armando can prove that Captain Howard was innocent.
警监去世前正在调查这些受贿的警官
Cap was onto these dirty players.
阿曼多告诉你的
Armando told you that
是的 这就是他们想杀死霍华德警监的原因
Yes It's the reason they wanted Captain Howard dead.
阿曼多可以认出下令袭击警监的人
Armando can ID the guy that ordered the hit on Cap.
有名字吗
He have a name
没有 但知道对方长什么样
No But a face.
我知道你们可以做到 好吗
Listen I know y'all can do this All right
转移阿曼多 带他去迈阿密一个安全的地方
Just transfer Armando Get him to Miami Get him to a secure location.
我们审问他 拿到他的证词 给他一些照片
We'll debrief him We'll get his testimony We'll get some pictures in front of him.
但请马上去做
But please do it now.
这些人试图掩盖真相 而且他们不会停手
These guys are tryin' to cover their asses and they are not gonna stop.
这是为了霍华德警监
Do it for Captain Howard.
对霍华德警监不利的证据确凿无疑
Look the evidence against Captain Howard is overwhelming.
如果我选择这样做 也是为了你
If I'm doing this I'm doing it for you.
好 我们转移阿瑞塔斯吧
All right let's transfer Aretas.
你陪他 把他带到迈阿密的冰屋 审问他
You'll accompany him get him to igloo here in Miami do a debrief.
但我是因为相信你 才冒这么大的风险
But I'm sticking my neck out and I'm trusting you.
如果他是骗人的 那我就完了
If he turns out to be bullshit then it's gonna be my ass.
所以别把我害了 迈克
So don't screw me Mike.
谢谢你
Thank you.
什么事
Yeah
我们找到了佐伊·庞德的储物柜
We found Zoe Pound's storage unit.
我们去拿文件 然后收藏在我的船屋
We'll go get the files then take them to my houseboat for safekeeping.
好 继续 找到后告诉我
All right stay on it Let me know when you got it.
请交出你的枪支 枪械将于着陆后还给你
Please surrender your firearms They will be returned to you upon touchdown.
你还好吗
You good
非常好
Never been better.
大约需要45分钟
It's about 45 minutes.
迈克 我没打算告诉你
Mike I wasn't even gonna tell you this
但在我们在一起的前世之一
but in one of our previous lifetimes together
你曾是一只驴
you were a donkey.
而且我是你的主人
And I owned you.
你很固执 迈克
You were a stubborn ass Mike.
你过去常咬人和吐口水
You used to bite and spit.
你很坏
You were nasty.
但我不是好主人 因为我总会打你
But I was a terrible owner you know because I used to beat you.
因为你不听话
Because you wouldn't listen for shit.
也许我打得让你感到羞耻 迈克
And maybe I beat some kind of shame into you Mike.
现在我意识到我伤害了你的灵魂
And now I realise I was scarring your soul.
你错过了午睡
You miss your nap
迈克 我在尝试向你道歉
Mike I'm trying to apologise to you.
你的小被子不在这里 但你可以闭眼休息
We don't have your blankie but you could just rest your eyes.
你当驴子时就是这样 好吧
That's exactly how you was as a donkey Mm kay.
就是那副鬼样子 我明白了
That's that shit there I get it.
你需要我帮忙系安全带吗
You need some help with your seat belt
不用 驴子
No Donkey.
嘿 布莱恩特 我是布朗森
Hey Bryant this is Bronson.
其他人之后还要回去
Other guys are on turnaround.
坐好
Take a seat.
怎么了
What's up
【设置自动驾驶】
读出来
Read the lines.
【设置自动驾驶】
读出来
Read the lines.
美国法警724航班 我们有紧急情况
US Marshal flight 724 we have an emergency.
我们的囚犯在迈阿密警察劳瑞和伯内特的帮助下越狱了
Our prisoner has escaped custody with the aid of Miami PD Lowrey and Burnett.
这里有倒下的警员
There are officers down.
求救 他们冲着驾驶舱来了
Mayday mayday They are coming for the cockpit.
我重复 他们正在劫持CH 47
I repeat they are hijacking the CH 47.
请所有地面单位回应
All ground units please respond
把劳瑞的枪给我 收到
Give me Lowrey's gun Copy.
快走
Go go
去找劳瑞
Get Lowrey.
我们走
Let's go
我们不惧暴风雨 王八
We welcome the storm motherfu
把我从这该死的牢笼里救出来
Get me out of this fucking cage
马克斯
Marcus
迈克
Mike
太重了
It's too heavy
别放手
Don't let go
抓住驾驶杆
Grab the stick
你怎么会开飞机
Where the hell you learn how to fly
我是个毒贩 向右
I'm a drug dealer man To the right
他用了我的枪
He was using my gun.
他们究竟是怎么登上美国法警直升机的
How the hell did they get on a federal transport
我们必须分头行动
We need to split up.
我们要在一起
We're gonna stay together.
谁说的
Says who
我不是在问你
I'm not asking you.
我在告诉你 我们要在一起
I'm telling you We're stayin' together.
别挡我的路
Fuck outta my way.
嘿 哪里 放开我
Hey Where Get the fuck off me.
喂
Hey Hey
听好
Look.
你是唯一能指证幕后主使的人
You are the only person who can identify whoever is doing this
我们活下去的唯一方法 就是先抓住他们
The only way that any of us stays alive is if we get them before they get us.
根本没有我们
There's no us There is no us
该死
Damn.
劳瑞的基因还真是让人头大
That Lowrey DNA is a bitch.
你俩的劲儿都这么大
Y'all some strong motherfuckers.
好 这样吧 大家放松 我数到三
Okay Now look everybody unflex On three.
一 二
One Two
就是这样
There you go.
霍华德警监给我们留下了文件 这些文件会告诉我们是谁干的
Captain Howard left us files that's gonna tell us who's doin' this.
都在东恩那里
Dorn has 'em.
我们只需要回到迈阿密
We just have to get back to Miami.
你最好别拖慢我
You better not slow me down.
丢了你们的电话
Lose your phones.
你跟紧我 否则我就让你自生自灭
You keep up with me or I leave you in the dirt.
现在你已来到我的世界
You're in my world now.
迈克 我们必须想一想
Hey Mike Look we gotta think about this.
我知道你要跟他走 因为他是你的 儿子
I know you wanna move with him you know because he's your son
哇 别那样说
Whoa whoa Don't air quote that.
不 我没有 我只是说我知道你在尝试保护他
No I didn't I'm just sayin' I know why you tryin' to protect him.
因为他是 家人
'Cause he family
你这样做和刚刚没什么差别
Hey Movin' the air quotes down to your hips doesn't un air quote them.
就直说他是我儿子吧
Just say he's my son.
他是你儿子呀 不
He's your son No no.
手掌向上就像你试图说：噢 他其实不是我儿子
Palms up is like you tryin' to say oh he's not really my son.
噢 你儿子走掉了
Oh Well your son's gettin' away.
混蛋
Shit.
如果你的人在执行某任务 最好通知我们
If your men are on some kind of op you might wanna pull us in.
不然 这对他们来说不太好
Otherwise it doesn't look good for them.
朱迪
Judy.
尸体的身份都确认了 对 但有三人下落不明
You ID the bodies Roger We got three unaccounted for.
劳瑞 伯内特和阿雷塔斯
Lowrey Burnett and Aretas.
这些混蛋 该死
Motherfuckers Fucking
见鬼
Shit.
好 听好了
All right Listen up
我们有三名嫌疑人 他们都携带武器 而且很危险
We have three suspects armed and dangerous out there.
给我把他们抓回来
And I want them back.
我们走
Let's go
等等 朱迪
Hold on Judy.
三个 嫌疑人
Three suspects
你觉得这里发生了什么事
What do you think is happening here
你觉得呢
What do you think
播放音频
Play the audio.
美国法警724航班 我们有紧急情况
US Marshal flight 724 we have an emergency.
我们的囚犯在迈阿密警察劳瑞和伯内特的帮助下越狱了
Our prisoner has escaped custody with the aid of Miami PD Lowrey and Burnett.
有警官倒下 求救
There are officers down Mayday mayday.
不是吧 你不会相信迈克和马克斯会这样做
Come on you can't possibly believe Mike and Marcus would do this.
你自己说的 劳瑞一心想让儿子出狱
Nah you said it Lowrey was obsessed with getting his son out of prison.
别急 朱迪
Slow down Judy.
这里不是迈阿密 塞卡达
This isn't Miami Secada.
这些是我的逃犯 全都是我职权管辖范围
These are my fugitives and right now the whole world is my jurisdiction.
你们认识了一辈子 你怎么能这么说
You've known them your whole life How can you even suggest
我认为这是迈克和马克斯策划的吗
Do I think that Mike and Marcus planned this
也许不是
Probably not.
但当涉及到家人时 人们会做他们通常不会做的事
But people do things they wouldn't normally do when family's involved.
根据我的经验 无辜的人不会逃跑
In my experience innocent men don't run.
我们能不能先分析 你能不能做好自己的工作
Can we stop and think before Are you capable of doing your job
因为我必须继续调查
'Cause I need to move on.
他们还活着
They survived.
什么意思
What the fuck you mean they survived
现场没有尸体 美国法警将其视为搜捕行动
No bodies on site US Marshals are treating it as a manhunt.
这些人就是死不了
These guys just refuse to die.
他们是通缉犯
They're wanted men.
执法部门和媒体现在是我们的朋友
Law enforcement and media are our friends now.
三名逃犯的追捕行动
A manhunt for three fugitives
在南佛罗里达州引起了轩然大波
is sending shock waves across South Florida.
弹道报告与从尸体中找到的子弹相符
Ballistic reports have matched the bullets recovered from the bodies
鉴于最近发生的事件 您打算退出市长竞选吗
Are you planning on dropping out of the mayor's race in light of the recent events
目前搜捕工作正在进行中
The manhunt is currently underway.
联邦调查局正在协助美国法警逮捕这些人
The FBI is assisting US Marshals in bringing these men in.
劳瑞 伯内特和阿雷塔斯应被视为有武器且危险
Lowrey Burnett and Aretas should be considered armed and dangerous.
这些人杀害了其他专业执法人员
These are individuals who have killed fellow law enforcement professionals.
如果你看到什么 请及时举报
If you see something say something.
在道上悬赏
Put a bounty on the streets.
通知城里每一个黑帮 让他们为悬赏而战
Get it to every gang in the city and let them fight for it.
五百万
Five mil.
我们赶快去抓这些混蛋
Let's go get these motherfuckers.
宇宙太疯狂了 不是吗
The universe is crazy ain't it
看我们
Look at us.
今早起床时没人料到我们会走到这一步吧
I bet none of us thought when we woke up today this is where we'd be.
你离开了监狱
You outta jail.
我俩要进监狱了
We goin' to jail.
命运真幽默
This shit is special.
迈克
Mike
你有什么想对阿曼多说的吗
Is there anything you would like to say to Armando
你怎么那样说呢 没有
Fuck you talkin' to me like that No.
迈克 就是现在 向你儿子说出来
Mike this is a moment Express with your son.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这样就对了嘛
That's what I'm talking about.
为了什么 为了一切
For what For everything man.
看来我爱的人都遭遇坏事 所以
Seems like bad shit happens to anybody I love so
我开始想也许我被诅咒了
Startin' to think maybe I'm cursed.
我只是觉得
I just feel like
也许是我连累了你
maybe I cursed you.
你没有
You ain't fuckin' cursed me.
大家都会遇上不好的事
Bad shit happens to everybody.
从来都不是你一个人的事
Ain't always about you.
阿曼多
Hey Armando.
不知我是否跟你说过 但几个星期前我死了
I don't know if I told you this but I died a couple of weeks ago.
很遗憾听到这个消息
Sorry to hear about that.
噢 不 是我经历过的最好的事情
Oh no The best thing that ever happened to me.
那次经历太不可思议
Shit's wild.
但你们
But y'all
你们就是我活过来的理由
Y'all the reason I came back.
嘿
Hey.
大家 抱一个
Everybody bring it in.
来 抱一个 来吧
Come on bring it in Come on.
什么
What
这就对了 阿曼多
There you go Armando.
这就对了 这就
There you go There you
你俩这逃犯当得太不合格了
Y'all are some terrible fuckin' fugitives.
你以为自己是马克斯·温弗瑞吗
So what are you fuckin' Marcus Winfrey
什么 看吧
What Now see
你让我们看起来很软弱 好像不知如何逃跑
You makin' us look soft like we don't know how to be on the run.
【第二修正案才是美国自己的国土安全部】
最好先给你找一身别的衣服穿
Better get you out of this.
喂
Hey
那孩子真固执 就像他父亲一样
That boy hard headed Chip off the old block.
瞧瞧我发现了什么
Well what we got here
该隐 过来看看
Hey Cain come take a look at this
你们这些小伙子在干什么
What are you boys doin'
小伙子
Boys
你们在偷我们的衣服 看起来是这样
Are y'all stealing our clothes Looks like it.
种族主义
Fuckin' racism.
就因为我们是黑人 你们就觉得我们偷了你们的烂东西
Y'all think just because we Black we stealin' your shit
这些是我自己的黑人服装
Now these are my own Black clothes
今天我从我的黑人衣柜穿上的
that I put on today from my own Black closet.
马克斯 什么
Marcus What
看你衣服上写了什么
Look at your shirt.
【外衫印刷字】纯种白人男孩
这东西怎么会在我的黑人衣柜
How'd this get in my Black closet
不如你给我们唱一首瑞芭的歌
Why don't you boys sing us a little Reba song.
瑞芭 瑞芭 好
Reba Reba Oh yeah.
请
Oh please.
那 因为他介绍瑞
That's 'Cause he put He put me on to Reb
哪一首 你们想听哪首
Which one Which y'all Which one
唱你最爱的
Sing your favourite.
她有很多 因为她有许多热门歌曲
Oh she got plenty of them 'Cause she got hits.
是快节奏的歌吗 还是慢的 对 记得那首吗
Was it the up tempo song Or the slow jam Yeah yeah remember the one
是那首慢的 哥们 噢 好
It was the slow one nigga Oh okay.
早上你伤害了我 是的 因为她受伤了
You hurt me in the morning Yes 'cause she was hurt.
晚上你伤害了我 对了
You hurt me at night Yes yes.
但我已改变 改变
But I've changed Changed
我很坚强 我是个女人
And I'm strong I'm a woman
我是个坚强的黑女
I'm a strong Black wom
我是个坚强的女人
I'm a strong woman
是的 因为她不是黑人
Yeah 'cause she's not Black.
然后
And then
你该怎么办
What you gonna do
你该怎么
What you gonna d
那不是瑞芭的歌
That ain't no Reba song.
这是她的混音带里的
It's from her mixtape.
混蛋
Goddamn it
对不起 我们会还回来
We're sorry We'll bring it back
我们没有因为我们是黑人而偷你的东西
We're not stealing your shit because we Black
你是否爱过她
Did you ever love her
什么
What
我妈妈 你是否爱过她
My mother You ever love her
他正在表达
He's expressing.
我肯定爱过她
I definitely loved her.
然后你出卖了她
And then you sold her out.
我做错了
I made some mistakes.
我也是你的错误
Like me.
你知道我不是 等等 阿曼多
You know that is not what I was trying Now wait a damn minute Armando.
他正在努力弥补
He's trying to make up for it.
他不欠你什么
He don't owe you a damn thing.
好 等等 马克斯 你太严厉了
All right hold on Hold on Marcus You're just You're being aggressive.
我做爸爸很久了 他必须听的 迈克
I've been a dad a long time He needs to hear this Mike.
他需要一些严厉的爱
He needs some tough ass love.
阿曼多 也许他确实亏欠了你
Armando Maybe he does owe you something Okay
你妈被他骗了
Your mom being deceived by him.
你出生在布满谎言的监狱里
You being born in prison in a web of lies
这使你变成一个冷血杀手
that turned your ass into a stone cold fuckin' killer.
是的 你是一个杀手
Yeah You're a killer.
但这男人由始至终是真诚的
But this man through it all has been nothing but solid.
那是什么年度之父的废话
That's some father of the year shit right there.
是吗
Is it
你那很烂的教养方式把卡车弄坏了
Your wack ass parenting broke the truck.
我的错
My bad.
是的 坏了
Yeah nah that's dead.
我们离塔比莎的夜店不远
We're not far from Tabitha's.
不 迈克 你知道那女人是疯的
No Mike You know that woman's crazy.
没错 但她喜欢我
Yeah but she likes me.
我不认为她有你想的那么喜欢你
I don't think she likes you as much as you think.
小马离这里大约两英里 小马 是什么
The Pony's about two miles from here What's The Pony
我需要美图分享 社交 更多的性爱
I need my Instagram I need my Friendster I need more sex.
我需要更多男人涌入这个夜店
I need more men in this club.
你们都很美 快去上班
You all look beautiful Now get back to work.
迈克·劳瑞 竟然是你
Mike Lowrey Damn.
你好吗 塔比莎
What up Tabitha
你们有麻烦 对吧
So y'all in trouble huh
是的 我们需要帮忙
Yeah we need some help.
我们需要一些衣服 可不是嘛
We need some clothes No shit.
一辆车和几部手机
A ride and some phones.
是 还有一些枪
Yeah Guns too.
那是我儿子 阿曼多
That's my son That's Armando.
你有一个西班牙小儿子
You got you a little Spanish son
是的 说来话长
Yeah it's a long story.
你能帮我们吗
Can you hook us up
你要的我都有 但你能给我什么
I mean I got all that but what you gonna do for me
什么意思 我们会付钱
What you mean We good for that.
你本来可以
You were.
但你们现在是逃犯 所以
But you guys are men on the run now so
你需要什么
Well what you need
我需要什么
What I need
我要你取悦我
I need you to eat this pussy.
我不做 知道吗
I'm not doin' that all right
哇 等等 迈克 你想想
Whoa hold on Mike hold on Think about this.
你说枪和手机 对吗
Now you say guns and phones right
这样吧 你也知道迈克结婚了
Okay well look you know Mike's a married man.
所以呢
So
所以他需要一些合理的推诿
So he's gonna need some plausible deniability.
我要你躺下来 伸出你的舌头
So I'mma have you lay down and stick out your tongue.
接下来由你来做
And you gonna have to do the rest.
我可以那样做
I can fuck with that.
继续 宝贝 不 马克斯
Oh yeah go on baby No Marcus.
你只需要闭上眼睛 迈克 不行
All you gotta do is close your eyes Mike No
我需要照片 你会拍照吧
I'mma need pictures You know how to take pictures right
我们没时间了 请你别再开玩笑
Hey We don't have a lot of time I need you to stop fuckin' around.
我没有开玩笑
Oh I'm not fuckin' around.
好 我们走
All right hey let's go.
等一下
Wait hold up.
你妈的坐下
Sit your motherfuckin' ass down.
塔比莎 你在做什么 你在做什么
Hey Tabitha what is you doin' What is you doin'
坐下 你们都坐下
Sit your married ass down You get y'all asses down too
完了 大家坐下
Shit Everybody sit down.
坏孩子在我这里 我们去领钱吧
Hey I got the bad boys right here Let's get that money.
塔比莎 闭嘴
Hey Tab Shut the fuck up.
等等 我不明白
Hold up I'm confused.
你不要他舔你
You didn't want him to licky licky
你的人头有五百万美元悬赏金
There's a $5 million bounty on your head.
我需要那笔钱 我只是在拖延
I need that money I was just stalling.
太贱了 他差点就做了
That's That's cold He almost did that shit.
才没有 马克斯
He did not Marcus.
我说了她不喜欢你
I told you she didn't like you.
站起来
Get the fuck up.
死活都有悬赏哦
The bounty is dead or alive.
别犯傻
Don't be stupid.
阿曼多
Hey Armando.
如果你活下来 我会让你
If you live I'll let you
什么
What
我说如果你活下来 来找我
I said if you live motherfucker holler at me.
他有点可爱
He was kinda cute.
我们收到一个举报
We got a tip.
确认是我们的逃犯
Positive ID on our fugitives.
行动开始
Let's do this.
迈克 我打算开始行动
Mike I'm about to make my move.
不行 跟着这些人走就是了
No the fuck you're not You about to go wherever these men are taking us.
我不去
Oh I'm not goin'.
前面三个我来处理 后面六个由你对付
Now I'll take the three in the front you take the six in the back.
马克斯 我们没有任何武器
Marcus we do not have any weapons.
倒数五 四 三
In five four three
该死
Fuck
糟了 是这王八蛋
Ah shit This motherfucker.
混蛋 你想干什么
Fuckboy fuckboy Whatcha gonna do
迈克
Ayo Mike
小白兔拿枪可没趣了 是吧
Ain't no fun when the rabbit got the gun huh
等等 你认识这人
Wait you know this guy
是的 几年前我用锤子打了他
Yeah I hit him with a hammer a couple years ago.
你以为我忘了曼尼牛排店的那件事
You think I forgot about that fucking ho shit you pulled off at Manny's Prime Rib
我怎么让你们两个抓住我的
How the fuck did I let you two catch me
迈克 我要我的五百万
Mike I want my five million.
马克斯
Marcus
我把我兄弟们都带来了 整个帮派都在
You see I got the fam with me The streets
我们可以轻松简单地完事 否则就开战
We could do this nice and easy or we can go to war
因为我准备开战了
'Cause I'm fucking war ready
你在干什么
What are you doing
不
No
快走
Go go go go
退后
Back up Back up Back up
不
No No
挡风玻璃雨刷液是易燃的
Windshield wiper fluid is flammable
我怎么知道 我又不是科学家
How the hell am I supposed to know that I ain't no damn scientist
大家冷静 火在外面
Everybody relax The fire's on the outside.
糟了
Oh shit
现在到里面了
Now it's on the inside
完了
Shit
好吧
Okay.
大家出去
Everybody out Everybody out
混蛋
Shit.
开门
Open the damn door
我们感觉到你在里边 小子 开门
We can feel you right there boy Open the door.
嘿
Hey
开门 肌肉奶
Open up Muscle Milk.
拜托 你在干什么
Come on man What the fuck is you doing
没什么 我现在不太方便
Nothing It's just not a great time for me right now guys.
我们现在也不太方便
It's not a great time for us either.
大约一个小时后我们再见面
Okay let's reconvene in like an hour or so.
宝贝 沐浴露没了
Babe we're out of body wash.
不是吧
What the hell
我们找到你们了
We found you guys.
我们在恋爱 好吗
We're in a relationship Okay
好
Oh okay All right.
我无法忍受偷偷摸摸
Sneaking around has been destroying me.
我们是几个月前在一起的 这不会影响我们的本职工作
It started about a couple months ago It will not affect our professional lives.
除了在货车上那一次
Except for that one time in that van.
我不会道歉的 没什么好道歉的
I am not sorry Nothing to be sorry about.
你知道的 人们会做那种事
Yeah you know I mean people do that shit.
你们没事吧 我们很好 我想
Are you guys okay Yeah we're good I wanted to
搞什么 好 哇
What the fuck Okay Whoa whoa.
卡丽
Hey Kelly Kelly.
我叫你在外面等一下
I asked you to wait outside for a second.
别激动 卡丽 他和我们是一伙的
All right Kelly he's with us.
他不能在这里
He can't be here.
这是我儿子 阿曼多
This is my son Armando.
我知道他是谁 所以他不能在这里
I know who he is and that's why he can't be here.
我很相信你 迈克 但我肯定不相信他
I trust you with my life Mike But I as sure as shit don't trust him.
我相信他
I trust him.
那带他去你家
Then take him to your house.
迈克 让我和她谈谈好吗
Hey Mike Can I have a second with her please
好的 请便
Yeah yeah Please.
亲爱的 放轻松
Hey sweetie Relax Relax.
过来一下
Come here for a sec Come over here for a second.
我们俩都有可能坐牢
We could both end up in jail.
给他一个机会 对 给他一个机会杀光我们
Give him a chance Yeah give him a chance to kill us all
这事超出常规了
This is some dysfunctional shit.
她没事了 看起来不像
She's fine She don't look fine.
我没事了 是 没错
I'm fine Yes you are.
你说什么 行了 行了
The fuck you say All right all right.
是语言文化差异 他说的是英语
It's the language barrier It was English.
肯定是英语
It was definitely English.
谢谢你的衣服
Thanks for the drip.
好 我们正在汇总所有数据
Yeah Okay we're aggregating all the data.
有超过100小时的视频 200多个音频单元
There's over 100 hours of video 200 units of audio.
我们正在索引所有音频 视频和地理定位IP网络数据
We're indexing all audio video and geo located IP network data
创建视野图并制定目标区
to create a sight picture and develop a target package.
基本上 要仔细筛选来找到那混蛋
Basically you sifting through all this shit to find the guilty motherfucker.
没错
Bingo.
东恩
Hey Dorn.
你能安全地让我进入远程监控吗 我想看看家人
Can you safely get me into my Ring app I wanna see my family.
好 我们有自己的VPN和路由器 你用户名是什么
Yeah we got our own VPN and router What's your username
马克斯37
Marcus37.
密码
And password
士力架89
Snickers89.
我很快就能回家了 宝贝
Almost home baby.
我们开工吧 这里有很多事要做
Hey let's get to work We got a lot to get through here.
我们到底要找什么
So what exactly are we looking for
我们正在寻找下令袭击警监的人
We're looking for the guy who ordered the hit on Cap.
阿曼多可以认出他
Armando can ID him.
这个混蛋就是我的白鲸
This fucking bastard has been my white whale.
过去的九年 我一直想用鱼叉刺死这个王八蛋
For the last nine years I've been trying to harpoon the son of a bitch.
但现在看你们的了
But now it's up to you.
难道我走进你家 教你如何做毒品
Ey Ey Ey Do I walk into your house and show you how to make cocaine
将它放大
Blow it up.
是他
It's him.
你肯定
You sure
就是那个下令袭击的人
That's the guy that ordered the hit.
找到名字了
Bam Got a name.
詹姆斯·麦格拉思 陆军游骑兵学校 反情报
James McGrath Army Ranger School counterintelligence.
詹姆斯·麦格拉思
詹姆斯·麦格拉思 陆军游骑兵学校 反情报
James McGrath Army Ranger School counterintelligence.
詹姆斯·麦格拉思
2005年之前一直部署在墨西哥
Deployed in Mexico until 2005.
曾与缉毒局 国防部武官办公室合作
Worked with the DEA Defence Attache's office.
糟了
Oh shit.
他被你的朋友 贩毒集团扣为人质
He was taken hostage by your friends the cartel.
他 在胁迫下 供出了整个小队
He gave up his entire squad under duress
这和酷刑无异啊
It's called torture man.
整个小队只有他活了下来
He was the only survivor.
警监一直都有他的犯罪证据
Cap had him the whole time.
他只是不知道
He just didn't know it.
喂
Hello.
嘿 是我
Hey It's me.
迈克 你在哪里
Damn it Michael Where are you
丽塔 我们要过来 我们有证据霍华德警监是无辜的
Rita we're coming in We got proof that Captain Howard is innocent.
什么证据
What proof
我们找到杀了霍华德警监的人
We got the guy that had Captain Howard killed.
阿曼多认出了他
Armando ID'd him.
也就是用直升机袭击我们的家伙 詹姆斯·麦格拉思
Same dude that attacked us on the chopper James McGrath.
丽塔 我们有多达十年的档案
Rita we got ten years' worth of files.
警监死前一直在调查这些家伙 我们全部查到了 是一整个网络
Cap was investigating these dudes We got 'em all It's a whole network.
明天我们就会交给你
We'll surrender to you tomorrow.
好 我们该走了
Hey look we gotta go.
迈克 什么
Michael what
你还好吗
You okay
他们会过来
They're coming in.
什么
What
迈克说他们有证据 证明霍华德无罪
Michael says they have proof that exonerates Howard
说明了一切
explains everything.
你是否还爱他
Do you still love him
什么
What
不
No.
但我相信他
But I believe him.
小心就是了 宝贝
Just be careful babe.
我们还去吃晚餐吗
Still going to dinner
好的
Yeah.
他们找到档案了
They have the files.
我们要让这看起来像贩毒集团 只说西班牙语
We need to make this look like cartel business Spanish only.
弹药准备好了 出发
Ammo's ready to go Let's go.
【触发动作传感器】
我们只需要一名人质 意思其余可射杀
We only need one hostage.
完了
Shit Shit Shit
各位 我们有麻烦
You guys We got a problem.
迈阿密指挥中心 有罪犯入侵居民家中
Miami Central Miami Central 29 in progress.
糟了 那是我家
Oh shit that's my house.
罪犯目标是同僚警察的家 请指示
Please advise MOS residence.
立即回应
Respond forthwith.
该死 糟糕 不 糟了
Fuck Oh fuck Oh no.
快 克莉斯丁
Come on Christine.
【未知来电】
该死 派一个警队去我家
Shit Get a unit over to my house.
快啊 雷吉 接电话 迈阿密指挥中心 又发生一起罪犯入侵事件
Come on Reggie Pick up Pick up Miami Central we have another 29 in progress.
请派警队到劳瑞警探的家庭住址
Please send units to Detective Lowrey's home address.
敌人倒下了
Enemy's down
雷吉 敌人正在逼近
Reggie You got incoming.
带家人到安全的地方 什么
Get the family to somewhere safe What
马上去 是 长官
Now Yes sir.
发生什么事 怎么了
What's happening What's going on
有人闯进屋子 我要保护你们的安全
There's people comin' in the house I gotta keep y'all safe.
请小心
Please be careful
雷吉 发生什么事 相信我 我爱你们
Okay Reggie what's happening Okay Trust me I love you.
该死 要命
Fuck Fuck
在你后面 雷吉
Behind you Reg
天啊
Oh damn
这人是谁呀 他是我儿子
Who the fuck is this guy That's my boy That's my boy
好棒
Damn
加油
Come on come on come on.
不
No no no
天啊
Holy shit
加油
Come on come on
天啊
Holy shit
把你们打得屁滚尿流 王八蛋们
Chitty Chitty Bang Bang motherfuckers.
我的零食就是你的 雷吉
Me snacks is your snacks Reggie.
好了 进去吧
All right come on.
迈克 你看到吗
Mike did you see that shit
接电话
Pick up the phone.
哇 迈克
Whoa Mike Mike Mike
等一下
One second.
凯莉
Callie.
我在电视上看到 我妈妈正在追捕迈克叔叔
I saw it on TV My mom is after Uncle Mike.
他不可能做了他们所说的一切
There is no way that he did everything that they're saying.
亲爱的
Sweetheart.
一切会好起来的 嗯
Everything is going to be okay Okay
好 那就好
Okay Okay
喂 是我 快离开房子
Hello It's me Get out of the house.
凯莉和我一起 带她走 马上离开
I've got Callie with me Take her and go Get out now
凯莉 躲到我后面
Callie get behind me.
迈克
Mike.
克莉斯丁
Christine
劳瑞先生
Mr Lowrey.
我在跟谁说话
Who am I speaking to
我想你知道我是谁
I think you know who you're speaking to.
我要你儿子
I need your boy
以及你敬爱的警监所藏匿的所有证据
and whatever evidence your beloved captain had squirrelled away.
用这些交换你的妻子
And for that you can have your wife.
稍后我会回电教你怎么做
I'll call you back with instructions.
混蛋
Aw shit.
该死的
Goddamn it.
我会去
I'll go.
让我的生命有价值一些
Let my life be worth something.
绝对不行
Never.
迈克
Mike.
他已经知道了
He knew.
什么意思
What do you mean
他已经知道我们会来
He knew we were comin' in.
他已知道我们有霍华德警监的档案
He knew we had Captain Howard's files.
他知道我们认出他
He knew we had ID'd him.
他怎么会知道
How
唯一与你交谈过的人是丽塔
Only person you spoke to was Rita.
不是丽塔
It's not Rita.
她对男人的品味也太差了
Damn she got bad taste in men.
【未知来电】
司法部一直在调查迈阿密警察局的腐败问题
Justice has been investigating the corruption in the Miami Police Department
有报告称已故警监康拉德·霍华德
with reports suggesting the late Captain Conrad Howard
喂
Hello
指挥警员与毒贩合作
was directing these elements in coordination with the cartels.
对霍华德的指控 间接针对劳瑞和伯内特
Allegations against Howard which allude to include Lowrey and Burnett
包括帮助毒贩将毒品运到佛罗里达州
and the operation range from helping cartels move the product into the state of Florida
以及交出关键证人 销毁证据
as well as giving up key witnesses destruction of evidence
甚至谋杀同事
and even the murder of fellow officers.
发生了什么事 我不知道
What's going on I don't know.
案件有了突破 我必须去警局
There's been a breakthrough in the case I need to get down to the station.
我要到那里去
I'm gonna head down there.
我跟你去
I'm coming with you.
你在发短信给谁
Who are you texting
我需要和办公室联系
Just Just gotta get in touch with the office.
联合部队
JTF.
必须通知大家
Gotta let everybody know.
亲爱的 别这样
Hey Honey Come on.
亲爱的 你在干什么 停手
Honey what are you doing Stop that.
你干什么 停手
What are you doing Stop it.
放开我 你在干什么
Let go of me What are you doing
还给我
Give it back to me Give it back
见鬼
Fuck
嘿 嘿 快起来
Hey hey come on.
你还好吗
You okay
看手机
Look at the phone.
你知道你完蛋了 对吧
You know you done fucked up right
你没事吧
You all right
对不起
I'm sorry.
没什么好抱歉的
Ain't got nothing to be sorry for.
我们会找到她的 警监
We'll find her boss.
除了在场的人 我不相信任何人
I don't trust anybody that's not standing right here right now.
我们每多牵扯进来一个人
Every extra person that we involve
都会增加他们知道我们要来的可能性
increases the likelihood that they know we're coming
这增加了克莉斯丁和凯莉
which increases the likelihood that Christine and Callie
无法逃生的可能性
don't make it out of there.
这意味着不要特警 法警和后援
That means no SWAT no marshals no backup.
只有我们
It's just us.
我从来没想过事情会这样发展
I never meant for it to go this way.
你认为事情会如何发展
How did you mean it to go
9/11之后 没有人关心毒品进入这个国家
After 9/11 nobody cared about drugs coming into this country.
为了确保边境安全 我们开始与毒贩合作
So to secure the borders we started to work with the cartels.
他们随时警告我们任何即将发生的恐怖活动
And they kept us informed about any terrorist activity coming our way.
效果很好 从那以后我们就没有再受到袭击
And it worked We haven't had an attack since.
我们正在保护这个国家
We were protecting this country.
你杀害警察 勾结毒贩将毒品带入国内而捞钱
You were killing cops and getting rich putting drugs into this country.
丽塔 所以你就杀了霍华德
Rita That's why you killed Howard.
他盯上你了 你要掩饰罪行
He was onto you You wanted to cover your tracks.
不 是麦格拉思
No That was McGrath.
他失控了
He's out of control.
丽塔 你听我说
Rita Just take a second.
我无意让这一切发展到这个地步
I never meant for any of this to go this way.
我只想知道 你是否是真心的
I guess I just need to know if it was ever real.
我一直都是真心的
It was always real.
我慌了 失控了
I panicked I lost control.
你是否爱过我
Did you love me
爱过
Yes.
我发誓
I swear.
那表示
Well that means
很好 声音样本采集完成
We good We got it.
99%声音匹配
99% voice match.
我完全不在乎 你这废物
absolutely nothing to me you piece of shit.
是我
Hey It's me.
到底发生了什么事
What the hell's going on
你搞砸了 就是这回事
You screwed up is what's going on.
我们暴露了 到了那里我会解释
We've been compromised I'll explain when I get there.
我们要转移人质 古巴 长期禁锢
We're moving the hostages Cuba Long term hold
这样 在解决这问题时 劳瑞 伯内特和阿雷塔斯就不敢轻举妄动
to keep Lowrey Burnett and Aretas quiet while we sort this out.
我乘水上飞机来 天一亮就到
I'm bringing a seaplane I'll be there at first light.
好 大家赶快收拾东西
All right pack this place up.
所有设备和人员准备转移
All equipment and personnel prepare to move.
我们要将人质转移国外
We're moving the hostages out of the country.
你的手怎么了
What happened to your hand
他们称之为哥伦比亚美甲
They call that a Colombian manicure.
这酷刑的绝妙之处在于
What's so great about it
它能让你感受最大程度的痛苦
is it's the maximum amount of pain
但又不会死去
but you don't die.
所以 你决定成为那个拿着钳子的人
So now you've decided to be the one holding the pliers.
每个人都会崩溃
Everybody breaks.
每个人
Everyone.
你丈夫
Your husband
将会跪在我面前
is gonna kneel down in front of me
并求我饶了你们的命
and beg for your lives.
然后你就会看着我杀掉他
And then you're gonna watch me kill him.
你不了解我丈夫
You don't know my husband.
我们没正式认识过 但是
Well not officially but
我期待再次和他见面
I look forward to seeing him again.
坏孩子
Bad boys Bad boys
唱嘛 迈克
Come on Mike.
坏孩子
Bad boys Bad boys
你打算怎么做
Whatchu you gonna do
对
Yeah.
敌人朝你袭来时 你打算怎么做
What you gonna do When they come for you
这就够了
That's enough dawg That's enough.
我们回头再继续唱
Okay well we'll circle back on that one.
好 飞机准备好了 20分钟后开始行动
All right The plane is ready We roll in 20.
这是一座废弃的游乐园 应该没有平民
It's an abandoned amusement park There should be no civilians.
飞机将从南边降落 在这一边
Plane is gonna land from the south On the one side.
马克斯和我从飞机上进击
Marcus and I will be on the plane.
阿曼多则从水中潜进突袭 两侧
Armando's gonna make his way in the water The two side.
卡丽 丽塔 这条路是一进一出
Kelly Rita This road is one way in one way out.
你们负责防守这路
You're holding that road.
东恩 你控制空中
Dorn you're gonna control the air.
无人机在空中 干扰已激活 通讯安全
Drones in the air jamming is active comms are secure.
他们会以为 洛克伍德正乘着飞机前去
As far as they know Lockwood is on his way with the plane
准备将人质转移到古巴
to move the hostages to Cuba.
当他们带着人质靠近飞机时 立即击毙劫匪
The second they get close to the plane with the hostages it's quick kills.
消除所有威胁
Neutralise all threats.
这些混蛋杀了很多好警察
These motherfuckers killed a lot of good cops.
他们绑架了我的妻子和凯莉
They have my wife they have Callie.
还袭击了我们的家人
They attacked our families.
今天我们绝不能输
We not losing today.
嘿
Hey.
飞机一降落 只要你搞小动作
We get on the ground you even flinch
就会在0.24秒里死去
you'll be dead in 24 seconds.
我同意
I concur.
我在外面的平台上有一人把风
I got one lookout on the platform outside.
二号楼的屋顶上有一名狙击手
I got one sniper on the roof of building two.
让我看看
Tee those up.
大家继续前进
Everybody keep moving.
那些是什么 鳄鱼
What are those Gators.
我以为这是一个废弃的鳄鱼公园
I thought it was an abandoned gator park.
真的被人们遗弃
Abandoned by humans.
其实这是一个古老的游乐园
It's actually an old amusement park.
它占地10英亩 2017年 飓风 艾尔玛 之后被废弃
It sat on 10 acres abandoned in 2017 after Hurricane Irma.
他们的主要景点是一只名叫杜克的白化鳄鱼
Their main attraction was an albino alligator named Duke
长16英尺 重900磅
who was 16 feet long 900 pounds.
据说它还在那里
And legend has it he's still there
糟了
Fuck that.
阿曼多可是从水上突袭
Armando's at his QTH.
人质现在出来了
Hostages are coming out now.
除麦格拉思外还有三人
McGrath plus three.
大家保持冷静
Everybody stay calm.
迈克
Mike.
迈克 能击中吗
Mike do you have the shot
不行 我无法开枪
Negative I do not have a shot I do not have a shot.
迈克 他就在那边 我无法开枪
Mike he's right there I don't have it I don't have it.
他们停下来了 为什么停下来
They stopped Why'd they stop
糟糕
Shit.
我们走
Let's go.
阿曼多 他们正在靠近你
Armando they're closing in on you.
他们看到他了 我不确定
Do they see him I don't know.
迈克 马上 现在是开枪机会
Mike now Your chance is now.
他们可能看见了他 知道我们在这里
They can see him They know we're here.
我无法开枪 不行 不行
I don't have it Negative Negative Negative.
你一定要开枪
You gotta take the fuckin' shot.
阿曼多暴露了
Armando's burnt.
该死 全面出击 开始行动
Shit Full green Engage.
卡丽 大家跟我上 快
Kelly get us there Go go go
【不得擅入】
【墨西哥玉米片】
敌人 码头西侧
Contact west dock side.
东恩 干掉那个狙击手
Dorn Take out that sniper
派出无人机
Sending the drone.
搞定
Got him.
不要发癫 迈克
Not now Mike
现在不行
Not now
没关系
It's okay.
不是你的错
Not your fault.
做个男人 大胆点吧 迈克
Cut that bitch ass shit out Mike.
我要可恶的迈克
I need Nasty Mike.
可恶的迈克
Nasty Mike
坏事发生了 但这并不意味着你很糟糕
Bad shit happens but that doesn't mean you're bad.
做一头固执的驴好吗 这就对了
Do that donkey shit a'ight That's what I'm talking about.
就那样 就像那样
That shit right there That's that shit right there.
坏孩子 坏孩子迈克 知道吗
Bad boy Bad boy Bad Boy Mike All right
你是邻里的大灰狼
You're the big bad wolf in the neighbourhood
不坏意味着坏 但坏就意味着好
Not bad meaning bad but bad meaning good
东恩 炸毁周边车辆 收到
Dorn take out the vehicles on the four side Copy.
走 快走
Go go Move it
长官 我们被袭击 失去了卡车和外面三个人
Sir We're taking heavies We lost the trucks and three guys outside.
该死的
Goddamn it
设置两侧射击位置 让他们进来
Set firing positions both sides Let 'em in.
去
Go.
法警霍华德 弹药车现场的热信号显示发生爆炸
Marshal Howard heat signature at the site of the AMMO van is showing explosions.
预计抵达时间15分钟
ETA 15 minutes.
东恩 我们需要掩护和内部情报 马上去
Dorn we need cover and we need eyes inside Go now.
烟雾来了
Here comes the smoke.
我在后面掩护你
I got your six.
打死那些混蛋
Shoot those motherfuckers
快把无人机打掉 快
Get those drones down now Go
快走
Move move move
上面
Eyes up
哦 妈的
Oh shit
这里就像乡巴佬侏罗纪公园
It's like redneck Jurassic Park in here.
我们马上离开这里
Let's get out of here now.
卡丽 去
Kelly go.
东恩 进去支援凯莉 我来追洛克伍德
Dorn back up Kelly inside I'm going after Lockwood.
宝贝 我来了
Babe I'm comin'.
阿曼多 去救凯莉
Armando go for Callie
放开
Let go
迈克
Mike
马克斯
Marcus
快走
Go
我没子弹了
I'm out
很高兴见到你 劳瑞先生
Nice to meet you Mr Lowrey.
手榴弹
Grenade
噢 不
Oh sh
天啊
Holy shit
撑住
Hang on
停
Stop
克莉斯丁
Christine
混蛋
Shit.
糟糕
Oh sh
迈克 让我来 不
Mike I got this No No no
我来了 宝贝
Here I come baby Here I come
不
No No No
马克斯
Marcus
什么 你后面
What Behind you.
天啊
Oh shit.
我能搞定 迈克
I got this Mike.
不过是小鳄鱼而已
It's just Dukey baby.
我的枪 枪掉进水了 就在你的脚边
Marcus my gun I dropped my gun in the water It's by your foot.
我不需要枪 迈克
I don't need no gun Mike.
滚开吧 鳄鱼
Begone gator.
你不该来这儿 小鳄鱼
This is not your place Duke.
我谴责你
I rebuke you
看吧 迈克
See Mike
这就是你命令宇宙的方式
That's how you command the universe.
枪呢 糟了
Where's the gun Where's the gun Oh shit
快走
Go go.
【警告】请勿将手置于鳄鱼坑内
那混蛋种族主义 迈克
That motherfucker racist Mike That motherfucker racist
迈克派我来
Mike sent me.
你一定要相信我
I need you to trust me.
快跑
Run.
跑
Run
撑住 快起来
Come on Come on Get up.
停
Stop
你快去 先别管我
Go I'll slow you down.
到达目的地
Eyes on location.
见鬼
Oh shit.
你活着吗
You alive
混蛋
Shit.
没事吧 嘿
Okay Hey.
丽塔 住手 你不会向我开枪吧
Rita stop this You don't want to shoot me.
你说得对
You're right.
过来 好 没问题
Come here Okay Okay It's okay.
我最讨厌政客
I fuckin' hate politicians.
【法警】
快走 走
Let's move Go go
散开 带他们到楼上
Fan out Take the team upstairs.
目标不在
No targets.
去上面
Go topside
【女儿凯莉的手链】
好 这里
Okay Okay here.
放我下来 没事的
Put me down It's okay Okay.
你还好吗 还好
You okay Yeah Yeah.
嘿
Hey.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我来过这里
I've been here before.
糟了
Oh shit.
你怎么让他抓住你了
How did you let him catch you
他真是太狡猾了 迈克
He's sneaky as hell Mike.
我和你妻子正在争论
Your wife and I were having a debate.
看来她对你的印象有些夸大了
She seems to have an inflated impression of you.
迈克 嘿 宝贝
Mike Hey bae.
尽管如此 这已经是尽头了
Nevertheless this is the end of the road.
他们其中一人就快死了
One of them is about to die.
你来选
You choose.
你不知道的是 麦格拉斯先生
What you don't know Mr McGrath
他们其中一人死不了
is one of 'em can't die.
你在说谁呢
Who you talking 'bout
一位智者告诉我 我将不得不做出艰难的选择
A wise man told me I was gonna have to make a hard choice.
在你选择之前 该要先和那个混蛋确认一下
You need to check with that motherfucker before you out here choosing shit.
你有五秒钟的时间 劳瑞先生
You have five seconds Mr Lowrey.
我们需要更多时间 先生
We gonna need some more time sir.
四 三
Four three
迈克 别做傻事
Mike Don't you do no dumb shit.
二
two
迈克 嘿 我在这里
Mike Mike Hey Hey I'm here.
混蛋向我开枪了
Motherfucker done shot me.
该死的
Aw damn.
来 让我看看 不 迈克 你这王八蛋又朝我开枪了
Here Let me check it Let me see No Mike Your donkey ass shot me again.
让我看看 拿开你手 迈克
Let me look at it Don't touch me with your donkey hooves Mike.
该死的
Damn man.
听好 我被逼开枪
Listen I had to fucking take the shot.
不 迈克 不
No Mike No.
马克斯 让我看看
Marcus Let me take a look.
你看到了吗 克莉斯丁
You see that shit Christine
我朝背心开枪 别再胡闹了 这个不重要好吗
I shot you in your vest Stop bitchin' It don't matter Okay
你知道你把一生奉献给了什么 克莉斯丁
You see what you done devoted your life to Christine
我已经看到阿瑞塔斯 正在接近
I've got eyes on Aretas Moving in.
糟了 那是朱迪
Shit That's Judy.
阿曼多 你听到吗
Armando do you copy
糟了
Oh shit.
妈妈 妈妈 不要
Mom Mom don't.
离她远点
Get away from her.
妈妈 马上
Mom Now
妈妈 听我说 你不明白
Mom listen to me you don't understand.
凯莉 我要你听我的
Callie I need you to listen to me.
我要你慢慢向右迈一步 向我走来
I want you to step slowly to your right and walk towards me.
妈妈 妈妈 我没事 好吗
Mom Mom I'm fine okay
凯莉 我要你走开
Callie I need you to move out of the way.
妈妈
Mom.
妈妈 别开枪 妈妈 他救了我 停
Mom don't shoot don't shoot Mom he saved me Stop
朱迪
Judy Judy
退后 迈克 把枪放下
Back off Mike Put the gun down.
他救了我的命
He saved my life.
求求你 妈妈
Please Mom.
妈妈
Mom Mom.
你中枪了吗
Are you hit Are you hit
我没事
I'm good.
你没事
You good
你做得很好
You did good You did good.
霍华德 你在哪里
Howard Where are you
霍华德 你听到吗
Howard Do you copy
霍华德 你在哪里
Howard what's your location
走吧
Go.
在我改变主意之前
Before I change my mind.
我们走
Let's go Let's go Let's go.
嘿 你还好吗
Hey You good You good
嘿
Hey.
拿去
Take this.
往南去 别回头
Head south Don't look back.
嘿
Hey.
我知道了
I got it.
乖一点
Be good.
你说了不算 警探
It's not up to you detective.
快点 这里有受伤的警察
Come on come on We got injured cops here.
我需要你马上把命令书给我
I need you to bring the writ to me now.
我知道
I know I know I know.
他怎么样了 他会挺过去的
How is he You know he'll pull through.
别吻他 克莉斯丁
Don't kiss him Christine.
迈克 下辈子 你就做我的一双鞋
Mike in our next life you coming back as a pair of my shoes.
而且我不会穿袜子
And I ain't gonna wear no socks.
还会踩着各种大便
And I'mma step in all kind of shit.
迈阿密检察官 市长候选人亚当·洛克伍德
Miami DA and mayoral candidate Adam Lockwood
以及前陆军游骑兵詹姆斯·麦格拉思
and former Army Ranger James McGrath
今天早上在交火中丧生
were killed this morning in a firefight.
据信洛克伍德和麦格拉思
It is believed that Lockwood and McGrath were the key links
才是迈阿密执法部门和贩毒集团之间的勾结人
between Miami law enforcement and cartels.
已故霍华德警监完全无罪
The late Captain Howard has been fully exonerated.
联邦调查局和迈阿密警察局目前正在追查同谋
Co conspirators are currently being rounded up by the FBI and the Miami PD.
对被定罪的杀手阿曼多·阿雷塔斯的搜捕仍在继续
The search for convicted killer Armando Aretas continues.
目前 逃犯仍然逍遥法外
The fugitive remains at large.
嘿 我的家人们
Hey hey hey My people.
特蕾莎在哪儿 她和小马克斯在秋千旁
Where's Theresa She's with Little Marcus by the swings.
嘿 我刚要煮给你们吃
Hey I'm about you hook you all up.
刚要煮给你们吃 请 我们很饿了
I'm about you hook you up Please We're starving.
看这个
Watch this.
搭档
Partner.
你这是要干什么
What's all this
你为什么要系围裙
Why you got on an apron
锻炼我的烧烤技巧
Work on my grill skills.
不 迈克 你去找别的烤架
No Mike you gotta earn the grill.
这需要调味料和温度 你不能直接用我的烤架
This takes seasonings and temperatures You can't just be cooking on my grill.
你的烤架 好笑了 这可是公共公园
Your grill Joker this is a public park.
你先看到的烤架并不是你的
You don't own every grill you see.
不如你去做点土豆沙拉 摆放桌椅
You know what Mike Why don't you go make some potato salad and set the table.
休想派我去做杂活
Oh you talking dirty.
这样吧 我不知道你脑子想的
Now look I don't I don't know what you got going on
烧烤独裁是怎么回事 但你小看我了
with your barbecue dictatorship in your mind but I ain't the one.
不管你喜不喜欢 我要在这个烤架上做饭
I'm cooking on this grill whether you like it or not.
迈克 抱歉 长官们
Hey Mike Excuse me sirs.
你在干什么 雷吉
What are you What you doin' Reggie
请求允许我煮鸡肉
Request permission to cook my chicken.
许可被拒绝 雷吉 去找其他地方吧 伙计
Permission denied Reggie Go ahead somewhere man.
脱掉你的工作服 去和孩子们一起玩
Take your smock off and go play with the kids.
听着 这是烧烤的男士区
Listen this is the man area of the barbecue.
恕我直言 我们很感激你拯救了我们所爱的人
Look you know what All due respect we appreciate that you did save people that we love.
我们很感激 好吗 是的 很感谢
We appreciate that right Yeah we appreciate that.
我们真心感激 雷吉 就是
We appreciate that from here Reggie Yeah.
你走开 没错
Now back the fuck up Yeah.
好 这样吧 我愿意妥协
All right look I'm willing to compromise with you.
你可以用那一半的烤架 它很小 这一半我来用
You can work that half of the grill It's small And I'll work this half.
他还站在那里吗
Is he still standing there
没错
Yes he is.
好奇怪
Huh that's weird.
是的
Yeah.
现在他觉得他很强大
He think he hard now.
你该让那混蛋知道 他今天不能在这里煮鸡肉
You need to let that motherfucker know he ain't cooking no chicken out here today.
迈克 他在屋内杀了15个人
Mike He killed 15 people at the house.
所以这事你管不了
So you not gonna handle this shit.
好 我会让那混蛋煮鸡肉
Yeah I'm gonna let that motherfucker cook the chicken.
他眼中有些奇怪的东西 我去做土豆沙拉
Yeah there's something weird in his eyes So I'mma make the potato salad.
我来摆桌椅 好
I'mma set the table Yeah.
请求允许了 雷吉 你来吧
Permission granted Reggie There you go.
【请勿离开,1:55:16后有情节彩蛋】
绝 地 战 警：生死与共
公元前305年
快点 继续走啊
Come on Bring your ass on.
天气太热了 没心情陪你耍性子
It's too hot out here for this shit.
如果我有一匹马就好了 至少他妈的可以骑
Wish I had a horse At least I could ride that motherfucker.
外面的空气多新鲜 我却只能闻到你的臭味
All this free air out here and I still smell your stinkin' ass.
我诅咒你 驴子
I curse you donkey.
我要诅咒你生生世世
I curse you for all lifetimes.
你这该死的
You mother
去你的 马克斯
Fuck you Marcus.